Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Greenwich House post-Simkhovitch records (NOT microfilmed)
  - Subseries 13: General (UNPROCESSED PORTION)
    - Day Care & Camp, undated (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Evening Classes; fall, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - People's Performing Company, undated (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Sr. Center, undated (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Single Parents Conference, undated (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Publicity; 1976 Antique Show (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Antique Show, 1977 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Antique Show, 1978 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Press releases, 1975 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Press releases, ca.1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Press releases, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - United Neighborhood House Auction/ Fair, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Camp, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Child Care- Breakfast Program, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Evening and After School Program, ca.1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - Counseling Center, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - Camp Fund Benefit, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - Senior Citizens, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - Pottery, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - Press releases, undated (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - St. Vincent's Hospital, 1970-1972 (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Preliminary Report on the Elderly in Greenwich Village- Pam Proctor, for NYC Dept. Of Mental Health and Retardation Services, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Report on the Elderly in Greenwich Village- NYC Dept. of Mental Health and Retardation Services, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - The Senior Villager, vol. 1, no.3, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 29)
    - The Senior Villager, vol.1, no.2, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 30)
    - Greenwich House Gazette, undated (Box 109, Folder 31)
    - Council of Greenwich Village Organizations (COGVO), undated (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Publicity (Fall), 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Anti-poverty publicity, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Publicity (Fall), 1964-1965 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Beryozka Russian Ballet- Music School Benefit, 1958 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Women's Christmas Advertising Luncheon, 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - 60th Anniversary Continuation, undated (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - General correspondence; Miriam Levensohn, 1967-1968 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - TVT; Brotherhood Award; nominations, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - TVT; GH Summer Group Work and After-School Programs, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Camera Club, ca.1967 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Children's Theatre, undated (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Child Care Center, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Council of Greenwich Village Organizations (COGVO), undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Council of Greenwich Village Organizations (COGVO), undated (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Project Head Start, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - TVT; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - MacDougal Alley, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - MacDougal Alley publicity, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - Teens- MacDougal, undated (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - MacDougal Alley- correspondence, photos, Camp Committee, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - MacDougal Alley- letters to press & radio, press releases, facts sheets on GH & MacDougal Alley, photos, 1964 (Box 110, Folder 22)
    - TVT; United Neighborhood Houses- Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - TVT; GH Counseling Center- treatment program for addicts, 1968-1969 (Box 110, Folder 24)
    - Board Meeting, 1968 (Box 110, Folder 25)
    - Board Meeting- 65th Annual Luncheon, Villager article, 1967 (Box 110, Folder 26)
    - Loose papers, undated (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - TVT; Miscellaneous- finances, 1950-1952 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - TVT; Gazette(February, June), 1975 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - TVT; Press releases, 1965, 1969, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Pottery Cards Brochures, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Antique Show- correspondence, undated (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Antique Show- advertising, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Antique Show- publicity, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Antique Show, 1964 (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Antique Show- publicity, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Antique Show- advertising, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Antique Show, 1965 (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Antique Show, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Antique Show- publicity, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Antique Show- advertising, 1966 (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Publicity, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - Benefit Performance- various, 1958-1961 (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Parsons, Henry McIlvaine, 1947, 1949 (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - Plum, Matthias, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - TVT; Press releases, undated (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Child Care Center, undated (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Thanksgiving Dinner, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Camp- Daily Feeding Reports, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Camp- Copake Falls, New York, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Camp Wanamaker, Island Heights, New Jersey- sale of, 1948-1949 (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence- Elizabeth Brown; Mary Simkhovitch, undated (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - TVT; Miscellaneous, undated (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Scheftel, Herbert, undated (Box 111, Folder 28)
    - Lower West Side Council- minutes, 1947-1949 (Box 111, Folder 29)
    - Women- chairmen and committee members, undated (Box 111, Folder 30)
    - Turnbull, Phillips R., 1949-1951 (Box 111, Folder 31)
    - Scheftel, Herbert, 1946-1951 (Box 111, Folder 32)
    - Zeckendorf, William, 1950 (Box 111, Folder 33)
    - Swope, Gerard, 1946-1949 (Box 111, Folder 34)
    - Wanamaker, Vivian, 1951 (Box 111, Folder 35)
    - Turnbull, John L., 1946-1950 (Box 111, Folder 36)
    - Residents' Manual-- Information and Instructions for Residents, undated (Box 111, Folder 37)
    - Simkhovitch, Vladimir G., 1951 (Box 111, Folder 38)
    - [Programs and Lists], 1945, 1954, 1983, undated (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - [Greenwich House Camp], 1945, 1956-1957, 1964-1965 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1946, 1947, 1951 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Filming Index Cards, 1994 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - [Newspaper Clippings], 1951, undated (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - 50th Anniversary- Mary K. Simkhovitch Memorial Plaque, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Trade School- Application for License, 1946-1947 (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - [Publications], 1941, 1946-1947, 1956 (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Greenwich House Promotional Material, 1941 (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - 18-20 Jones Street Sale of Property, 1947-1948 (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - [Public Relations], 1947, 1949-1950 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - General, A-D, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - General, S-Z, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Greenwich House Board of Managers- Correspondence, etc., 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Greenwich House Inter-Office Communication, 1951-1952 (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Scholarships, 1947-1948 (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Theatre, 1949, 1952 (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Annual Report, undated (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Annual Report, 1942 (Box 112, Folder 19)
    - Annual Report, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 20)
    - Annual Report, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report, 1948 (Box 112, Folder 22)
    - Annual Report, 1950 (Box 112, Folder 23)
    - Director's Reports, 1939 (Box 112, Folder 24)
    - Monthly Reports, 1942 (Box 112, Folder 25)
    - Monthly Reports, 1943 (Box 112, Folder 26)
    - Monthly Reports, 1944 (Box 112, Folder 27)
    - Monthly Reports, 1945 (Box 112, Folder 28)
    - Monthly Reports, 1946 (Box 112, Folder 29)
    - Monthly Reports- Bound Volume 1, 1919-1922 (Box 112, Folder 30)
    - Monthly Reports- Bound Volume 2, 1932-1935 (Box 112, Folder 31)
    - Greenwich House Workshop Papers, 1987 (Box 112, Folder 32)
    - Greenwich House Users Oral History and Interviews, 1986 (Box 112, Folder 33)
    - Greenwich House Oral History and Interviews, 1983-1986 (Box 112, Folder 34)
    - Annual Reports Publications, 1910-1946 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Antiques Show, 1951-1974 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Art Exhibit - "The 19th Century Heritage", 1950 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Bazaar - Third Annual, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Belgian Children's Art Exhibition, 1947 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Benefit, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Bulletin, Community Council Correspondence, General Correspondence, Pottery Miscellaneous, General Publicity Solicitation Forms, Theater, and Thrift Shop., 1953-1954 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Camp (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Camp Folder (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Camp Fund, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Camp Fund 1950, 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Camp Fund 1950 Printed Material (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Camp Carnival, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - Camp Fund, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - [Camp Issues], 1954-1955 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - Chamberlain, Joseph P. (Regarding Contributions), 1941-1951 (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - Chewery, William Ludlow, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Child Care Center, 1962 (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - Children's Art Workshop, 1947-1949 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Christmas Appeal 1950 (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - Classic Car Club CARavan, 1954-1962 (Box 113, Folder 21)
    - Contributors' List (Monthly), 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 22)
    - Cullman, Howard S., 1947, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 23)
    - Day Care for Older Adults (Box 113, Folder 24)
    - DeSapio, Mrs. Carmine G., 1951 (Box 113, Folder 25)
    - Dickerman, Marion, 1950 (Box 113, Folder 26)
    - Dorr, John V. N. (Regarding Contribution), 1949 (Box 113, Folder 27)
    - Executive Director's Report, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Family Service Committee, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - Farley, James A. (Regarding Contributions), 1947-1950 (Box 113, Folder 30)
    - Field, Marshall (Regarding Contributions), 1946-1950 (Box 113, Folder 31)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary Campaign- Honorary Chairman, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 32)
    - Fundraising Plans, 1947-1948 (Box 113, Folder 33)
    - Goebel, Marie Louise, 1949 (Box 113, Folder 34)
    - Greenwich House Council- Bylaws and Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 113, Folder 35)
    - ["Greenwich House News" and Press Releases], 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Group Work (Box 113, Folder 37)
    - [Holiday Materials and Miscellaneous Reports], 1946-1981 (Box 113, Folder 38)
    - House and School of Industry Publications and Antiques Show and Sale Programs, 1899-1938 (Box 113, Folder 39)
    - Lawrence, Mrs. John T., 1950 (Box 113, Folder 40)
    - Lists- Potential Contributors, Committees, and Area Businesses, circa 1948-1950 (Box 113, Folder 41)
    - [Loose Materials and Map of Greenwich Village], 1987, undated (Box 113, Folder 42)
    - Magowan, Doris Merrill (Mrs. Robert A.) Regarding Contributions, 1950-1951 (Box 113, Folder 43)
    - Maynard, Walter (Regarding Contributions), 1948-1951 (Box 113, Folder 44)
    - Membership Drive, Greenwich Village Area (Mark Van Doren), 1948 (Box 113, Folder 45)
    - Metcalf, Manton B. (Regarding Finances and Contributions), 1947-1951 (Box 113, Folder 46)
    - Michel, Clifford W. (Regarding Contributions), 1948-1950 (Box 113, Folder 47)
    - Minutes, Board and Executive Meetings, 1943-1951 (Box 113, Folder 48)
    - Mitchell, MacNeil (Regarding Contributions), 1949-1950 (Box 113, Folder 49)
    - Molloy, J.G.L. (Regarding Contributions), 1947-1950 (Box 113, Folder 50)
    - Moore, Mrs. Paul (Regarding Contributions), 1947-1951 (Box 113, Folder 51)
    - Music School Library, 1948 (Box 113, Folder 52)
    - Narcotics Problem, 1958 (Box 113, Folder 53)
    - [Opera Ephemera] (Box 113, Folder 54)
    - Pottery, circa 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 55)
    - Pottery, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 56)
    - Pottery, 1954 (Box 113, Folder 57)
    - Press Releases, 1951-1952 (Box 113, Folder 58)
    - Press Releases, 1952-1953 (Box 113, Folder 59)
    - Press Releases, 1953-1954 (Box 113, Folder 60)
    - Press Releases, 1962, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 61)
    - [Promotional Materials and Department of Health Permits], 1948-1955 (Box 113, Folder 62)
    - [Public School 41 Opening], 1968 (Box 113, Folder 63)
    - Schedule of Afternoon Activities, 1952 (Box 113, Folder 64)
    - Theatre Benefits, 1947-1949 (Box 113, Folder 65)
    - Thrift Shop, 1969-1979 (Box 113, Folder 66)
    - [Administrative Papers], 1938-1949 (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - [Antique Show], 1954 (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - Camp Appeal, 1960 (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - [Correspondence], 1950-1962 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - [Dexter Cooper and Charity Bailey], 1954, undated (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - [Fifth Avenue Extension], 1948, 1954, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Greek War Relief Association (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - [Greenwich House Arts and Crafts], 1982-1988 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Greenwich House- Deaccessions (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Greenwich House- Events Prior to 1951 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Greenwich House Photos (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Greenwich House Press Releases, 1973-1974 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Harvey A. Bashman, Jr., 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Briant S. Cookman, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Marshall Field, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - John V. N. Door, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Mrs. Samuel Dushkin, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - James A. Farley, 1950-1951 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - William H. M. Fenn, 1952-circa 1953 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Mrs. William C. T. Gaynor, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - [Greenwich House History], 1902-1994 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - H. Stanley Hillyer, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Mrs. John T. Lawrence, 1950-1951 (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Local School Board of District 9, 1915-1917 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Maps Related to Sale of Camp Wanamaker (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Walter Maynard, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Arthur P. McNulty, 1950-1951 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Manton B. Metcalf, Jr., 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 28)
    - [Miscellaneous Correspondence and Promotional Material], 1968-1979 (Box 114, Folder 29)
    - Mitchell, MacNeil, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 30)
    - J.G.L. Molloy, 1950, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 31)
    - Mr. Monica Correspondence (Box 114, Folder 32)
    - Joseph A. Monica (Box 114, Folder 33)
    - 1960 Music School Benefit- Piccolo Teatro, 1959-1960 (Box 114, Folder 34)
    - Narcotics- Publicity (Box 114, Folder 35)
    - Mr. and Mrs. George W. Naumburg, 1950, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 36)
    - NYC Board of Education (Mabel Spinney), 1915-1917 (Box 114, Folder 37)
    - Mrs. Francis T.P. Plimpton, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 38)
    - Matthias Plum, 1949-1951 (Box 114, Folder 39)
    - [Pottery Press Releases], 1959, 1963, undated (Box 114, Folder 40)
    - [Powers, Maxwell Correspondence], 1954-1955 (Box 114, Folder 41)
    - Publicity, Oct. 1947-Sept. 1948 (Box 114, Folder 42)
    - Publicity, Sept. 1948-June 1949 (Box 114, Folder 43)
    - Publicity, 1947-1949 (Box 114, Folder 44)
    - Publicity (Box 114, Folder 45)
    - 1965 Rehab- Offer to Greenwich House (Box 114, Folder 46)
    - Herbert Scheftel, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 47)
    - [Simkhovitch Correspondence and "The Settlement Primer"], 1919-1947 (Box 114, Folder 48)
    - Mary K. and Vladimir G. Simkhovitch, 1949-1952 (Box 114, Folder 49)
    - Louis R. Sprigg, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 50)
    - [Staff Information, Studio Portraits, and Miscellaneous], 1943, 1951, 1964 (Box 114, Folder 51)
    - Gerard Swope, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 52)
    - [Telegrams], 1960 (Box 114, Folder 53)
    - Television Fund, 1948 (Box 114, Folder 54)
    - Theatre Benefit- "The Gay Life", 1961 (Box 114, Folder 55)
    - 1960 Theatre Benefit- "Goodbye Charles", 1959 (Box 114, Folder 56)
    - [Theatre Correspondence], 1960 (Box 114, Folder 57)
    - Treasure Trove, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 58)
    - Treasure Trove- Contracts with Hickory Associates, 1949 (Box 114, Folder 59)
    - Phillips R. Turnbull, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 60)
    - Turnbull, Phillips R., 1951 (Box 114, Folder 61)
    - Visuals for Publications (Box 114, Folder 62)
    - W- Miscellaneous (Box 114, Folder 63)
    - Wanamaker, Mrs. Rodman- Chairman, Women's Committee- Fiftieth Anniversary, 1951 (Box 114, Folder 64)
    - Whitmarsh, Francis L., 1949-1950 (Box 114, Folder 65)
    - Francis L. Whitmarsh, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 66)
    - Mrs. Throop M. Wilder, 1952 (Box 114, Folder 67)
    - William Zeckendorf, 1950-1952 (Box 114, Folder 68)
    - Antiques Show-- Committee Teas, 1965-1967 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Antiques Show-- Dealers List, 1966 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Antiques Shows-- Financial Statements, 1959, 1962-1965 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Edward M. Barrows Correspondence, 1922 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Calendars of Christmas Activities, 1965-1969 (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Camp-- Correspondence and List of Children, 1984 (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Camp-- Rehabilitation of Physical Plant, 1960-1965 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Camp-- Rehabilitation of Physical Plant, 1964-1965 (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Camp-- Statements of Cash Position, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Child Care Center Correspondence, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Children's Art Classes, 1947, undated (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Council on Drug Addiction-- Correspondence (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Council on Drug Addiction-- Dr. Meiselas' "Narcotics" Statement (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Council on Drug Addiction-- Meeting, Mrs. Droutman, Quaker Committee On Social Rehabilitation, March 18, 1969 (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1966-1969 (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies-- Summer Volunteers, 1977-1980 (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Fiftieth Anniversary- Invitation Correspondence, 1951 (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Financial Report, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Fundraising Letters, 1951 (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Fundraising-- Printed Materials: Camp, undated (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Fundraising-- Printed Materials: Camp, 1948-1985 (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Fundraising-- Printed Materials: Christmas, 1947-1960, undated (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Fundraising-- Printed Materials: General Fund, 1953, undated (Box 115, Folder 23)
    - Greenwich House- General Correspondence, 1966, 1969, 1970 (Box 115, Folder 24)
    - Greenwich House Pottery School Historical Records Survey, 1988 (Box 115, Folder 25)
    - Group Work, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 26)
    - Gymnasium Repairs, 1955 (Box 115, Folder 27)
    - Job Training Partnership Act/Project Return Foundation Proposal, 1983 (Box 115, Folder 28)
    - Job Training Partnership Act/Project Return Foundation, 1983-1985 (Box 115, Folder 29)
    - MacDougal Alley, 1958-1960 (Box 115, Folder 30)
    - MacDougal Alley, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 31)
    - MacDougal Alley, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 32)
    - Music School Committee, 1960 (Box 115, Folder 33)
    - National Federation of Settlements Minutes, 1947-1948 (Box 115, Folder 34)
    - National Federation of Settlements Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 115, Folder 35)
    - National Federation of Settlements Minutes, 1952-1954 (Box 115, Folder 36)
    - National Federation of Settlements Minutes, 1955 (Box 115, Folder 37)
    - New York Women's Trade Union League, 1949 (Box 115, Folder 38)
    - Newsletter Greenwich House Spectator, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 39)
    - Maxwell Powers- Personal Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 115, Folder 40)
    - Printing-- Antiques Show, 1964 (Box 115, Folder 41)
    - Printing-- Antiques Show, 1965 (Box 115, Folder 42)
    - Saint Vincent's Hospital Correspondence, 1967 (Box 115, Folder 43)
    - Salaries- Employees (Box 115, Folder 44)
    - Senior Citizens Day Center and Monthly Reports, 1967-1969 (Box 115, Folder 45)
    - Sixtieth Anniversary, 1962 (Box 115, Folder 46)
    - Spring Vacation and Field Trip Program, 1977 (Box 115, Folder 47)
    - [Staff Directories, Activities List, and Press Releases], 1949, undated (Box 115, Folder 48)
    - Staff Roster, 1948 (Box 115, Folder 49)
    - 27 Barrow Street- Estimate on Repairs to Building, 1961 (Box 115, Folder 50)
    - United Neighborhood Houses, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 51)
    - Village Singers-- Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 115, Folder 52)
    - Village Singers-- Flyers and Programs, 1977, undated (Box 115, Folder 53)
    - Village Singers-- Member List and Mailing List, 1977, undated (Box 115, Folder 54)
    - Village Singers-- Press Releases and Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 115, Folder 55)
    - Village Singers-- Reports and Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 56)
    - Youth Council Minutes, 1947 (Box 115, Folder 57)
    - Lists, Blue Prints, and Two Bound Volumes of Press Clippings., circa 1915-1936 (Box 116)
    - Donor Cards (Box 117)
    - Donor Cards (Box 118)
    - Early photo exhibit (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS003, Folder 15)
    - Certificates, broadsides, posters, photos, 1915-1979 (Box 125)
    - Certificates, brochures, original artwork, Greenwich Village Carnival, 1913-2002 (Box 126)
- Series IX: Archived Website, Aug 25, 2009-ongoing
  Scope and Content Note
  Greenwich House, founded in 1902 by Mary Kingsbury Simkhovitch, is a social settlement house in the Greenwich Village section of New York City. Initially founded to help New York's immigrant populations adjust to life in a new country. The organization offers social and health services, cultural and educational programs, and opportunities for civic involvement to New Yorkers of all ages and backgrounds, including a chemical dependency program, classes in music and pottery, a nursery, and a senior center.